In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard, the
share price at this time is Rs 1536 and the
first support in the share is Rs 15 and the second
support is Rs 1425 and at this time the market cap of RS
Africa and the
company is Rs
75 thousand crores of
stock and the company makes a difference of 0.1
and here you can see that the
company has increased its profit in the markets,
now if we talk about share holding then
promoter's holding is 3.08
Amazing spider-man 370 and security
deposit 56 and public holding 13
point 65
and here you can see that
share
subscription was at this time you are getting a discount of
Rs 15, you can start trading and
if the share falls then you
can add some quantity to this hole, that's all
in this video, if you
miss the video then subscribe to the channel now